# Nicholas Trujillo

# Web Developer

75 N Valle Verde Dr Henderson, NV 89074

(702) 715-3233 nicholasrtrujillo@gmail.com

Portfolio nicktrujillo.github.io

# LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/nicholastrujillo1

# GitHub

github.com/nicktrujillo

# Dev.to

dev.to/nicktrujillo

#### Twitter

https://twitter.com/nickkrich

# **Technical Skills**

#### Proficient:

- JavaScript
- React
- Redux
- SQL
- PostgreSQL
- HTML
- CSS
- Git

#### Exposure:

- Node.js
- Express
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- Socket.io

I am a developer who specializes in creating web applications using JavaScript, React/Redux, Express, and other modern web tools. I have previous experience on the Operations team at a tech startup, but I have since developed a passion and skill-set for the engineering side.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Monzo Bank (mobile app) / Customer Operations Specialist

October 2019 - August 2020, Las Vegas, NV

- Handled all business operations tasks, from verifying customer identification documents to generating bank statements
- Communicated directly and honestly with customers, and developed a deep understanding of what the community really wanted from a digital bank in order to provide the most value
- Proactively spotted patterns in the actions of customers, identifying where we could change our processes, tools, or product to improve their experience
- Investigated and resolved complex payment or product-related issues
- Consistently achieved a 95-100% rating on Quality Assurance audits conducted regularly to ensure compliance with processes. Benchmark was 85%

## Clark County Water Reclamation District / Strategic Services Assistant

May 2015 - October 2019, Las Vegas, NV

- Supported the Assistant General Manager in the daily operations and management of the government wastewater treatment facility
- Represented CCWRD at public board meetings conducted by the county and shared information with the community about current and upcoming projects
- Represented CCWRD at local events such as the 2019 GreenFest and the UNLV job fair by overseeing designated information booths. Led the organization, planning, and logistics of these events
- Created and directed a video advertisement for a campaign that was played on the scoreboard at every Las Vegas Aviators baseball game

## **RECENT PROJECTS**

**Invitation Tracker** | code: Full-stack application where the user has the ability to mark a guest as going or not going, which then sends the guest's data to the Express server. The server consists of different routes that track who is going or not going. This project demonstrates my understanding of React Router and ability to create an Express server that stores and tracks data.

**React ToDo App** | <u>live</u> | <u>code</u>: This is a todo application that allows the user to create new todo items, mark items as completed, and remove items from the list. There is also a filter that can display all items, completed items, or active items. This project demonstrates my understanding of how React state works and how to manage that state with Redux.

### **EDUCATION**

**PunchCode** / Full-stack Web Development Bootcamp

August 2020 - November 2020, Las Vegas, NV

University of Nevada, Reno / B.S. Community Health Sciences

August 2014 - December 2018, Reno, NV